my man Vic.
How's it going, man? Good to see you.
Thanks for having us out here. Of
course, man. You want to go inside the
plane and talk there? You want to talk
here? Let's go check it out. Yeah, let's
go do it.
Now, what did you do to be able to
afford a jet? I want to get right into
it. I own the
largest in the United States. What was
the most amount of money you've made in
a single year? So, I will tell you that
in just in the last, you know, three or
four years, I probably added probably 85
million to my net worth. Are you
serious? 85 million. million to my net
worth. Have you ever been broke before?
January 2015, I had $78 to my name. I
took a screenshot of it actually and I
told myself that one day when I have my
own plane, I'm going to put that 78 on
my tail and I did last year. And you got
yourself a private jet. And I got myself
a private jet. How much did the jet
cost? I would say all of it is over 5
million bucks. $5 million. Is it safe to
say that you can fake a super car, but
you can't fake a private jet? You can't
fake a private jet. Even if somebody
gave you a jet, you still need $2
million a year to run the jet. You'd
have to have at least $2 million a year
to just run it. Just to run it. You
network with a lot of billionaires. So,
the guy that's coming on the plane with
me today, this guy's super rich, right?
He's super rich. Rich, rich. Real money
rich. One day I was picking him up for
his private flight, this was years ago,
and he's like, "And your last message to
somebody trying to own a private jet in
today's world." Give them the blueprint
right here. 60-second blueprint on how
somebody can own a private jet in
today's world. The 60-second blueprint
on how to own a private jet is this,
guys. So, I have a crazy story to tell
you. So, the last couple days, I was
filming out in Miami, Florida, and I get
a text message from one of the biggest
healthc care entrepreneurs in the entire
world. And he said, "James, I've been
seeing a lot of your videos recently
with people in Lamborghinis and
Rolls-Royces and at houses." But he
said, "You can fake a car, you can't
fake a private jet." And since he just
bought a jet, he invited me out to
interview him on his jet out in Tampa,
Florida before he flies out to Columbia.
But he didn't just invite me out to
interview him on the jet. He's flying me
out from Miami, Florida right now to
Tampa to interview him in this Golf Room
2 jet. We're flying out right now to go
meet up with Vic to figure out how he
became one of the most successful
entrepreneurs in the entire world. How
you can become a multi-millionaire in
today's world. So let's go link up with
Vic and go see what he has to say. Come
on.
[Music]
All right, you guys. So, we just landed
out here in Tampa. Let's hit him right
now to go meet up with the legend, Big
Vic Tip. Come on, my man Vic. How's it
going, man? It's good to see you. Thanks
for having us out here. Of course, man.
Of course. How was the flight? It was
great. Yeah, we appreciate you sending
the the PJs. and we came out from Miami
out here to kind of give them the
blueprint on how they can become a
multi-millionaire like you in today's
world. Can we make that happen? Let's do
it, man. Yeah. You want to go inside the
plane and talk there? You want to talk?
Let's go check it out. Yeah, let's go do
it. So, I got a question for you. So,
you know what my tail number means?
What's that? The four is the month I was
born in, which was April. And then the
78 is how much money I had to my name in
2015. You had $78. I had $78 to my name.
And I told myself in 2015, I'm not
kidding you. It's on my Instagram. I
actually took a snapshot of my bank
statement in 2015 and it was $78 and
maybe like 60. So I remember telling
myself, I said, "One day I'm going to
work really hard and when I get my own
plane, I'm going to put 78 on the tail
number." I love it. Isn't that crazy?
You turned that into an empire. Yeah, I
did. I I I worked really really hard and
took a lot of risk and a lot of
sleepless nights. So when I got my tail
number approved by the FAA and I put it
on there, it was like nobody knows what
it means except me, you know. Yeah. So
when you were at rock bottom down to
$78, what was that first actionable step
that you took? Cuz there's a lot of
entrepreneurs out there, maybe they're
motivated, but they don't know how to
actually start. What's that first step
everybody should take right now to start
kind of building that financial freedom?
You got to commit. People are like, "Oh
yeah, you got to commit." But I'm like,
"Really commit?" Like, there was nothing
more important to me than being
successful in accomplishing my goals.
Like nothing. like sleep wasn't more
important, oxygen wasn't more important,
like nothing was more important. And I
was willing to sacrifice everything that
you could possibly sacrifice and work as
many hours as I had to or needed to in
order to be successful. And I don't
think a lot of people commit to success.
Yeah. You you need a great idea, but
then if you have a great idea, but
you're not committed, you give up. Was
the sacrifice worth it? Was it all worth
it? Yeah, it's absolutely. Look, it's
it's worth it because of the level of
quality of life that you get to have
when you work really hard. You know, I'm
getting ready to fly to to Medigene. I
have an office there and I have a house
now in Medigene and so I'm going there
to work. I got 350 employees in in
Medigene. Can we ask you some questions
on the jet now? Yeah.
What did you do to be able to afford a
jet? I want to get right into it. So, I
own Blackstoneone Medical Services.
We're the largest provider of medical
sleep testing in the United States. We
have over 650 employees. I started the
company in my kitchen in 2012. You know,
I think at that point we were testing
maybe a couple of hundred patients a
month and actually in May of this year,
we we have now tested over a million
patients. So, you're in sleep testing,
but this is a very niche and specific
business in the healthcare sector. Some
people would argue maybe it's a little
bit unsexy. Everybody thinks that they
have to go build that next crazy tech
startup or go reinvent the wheel. Talk
to me about you finding this niche and
why this business in particular and how
it's been so successful. Well, you know,
I I found a problem that I wanted to
solve that I was passionate about. So, I
I don't believe that you can just make
money without passion because when
you're going to when you come across all
these hurdles and headaches and
problems, if you don't really love what
you do, you're going to give up. So, for
me, I really loved healthcare. I've
always loved healthcare. My parents
unfortunately died when I was in my
early 20s because they died of cancer.
So, I was exposed to the healthcare
world through that. And what I saw was a
a need and an opportunity to provide
great service. And so, for me, it was
like I'm passionate about healthcare. I
love the sleep industry. I love what it
stands for. Obviously, as you know, you
know, as young as you are too, like how
important sleep is, right? To recuperate
and regenerate your body. And so, I
thought, hey, this is a problem that I
think I can solve. And I wanted to do it
better than anybody else on the planet.
What correlation does sleep have on
people's success? You know, you hear all
these entrepreneurs, they talk about
work, work, work, work, work. I mean,
look at what's the guy I think is John
D. Rockefeller. When he was like 40, he
looked like he was like 80. Talk to me
about the correlation that you've seen
on sleep, health, and you know,
physical, financial, mental success.
Well, look, if if you're not rested and
wellfed, you're not going to work good.
So, you you got to be able to have your
brain working throughout the day. So,
you know, this whole idea that sleep
isn't important or that sleep is for
weak people, it's not just not true. You
need sleep. Now, there's variances. Some
people need 6 hours, like how much sleep
do you get? Honestly, not that not good.
Like 6 hours, 7 hours. 5 to 7 hours.
Okay. But are you able to function? I
am, but when I do that consistently,
then I start to kind of wear off at the
end of the day. Exactly. So if you're
running hard, you know, you're doing 12,
13, 14 hours of work and you're grinding
and you need to be focused, you need to
sleep. So for me, I I have to get at
least 6 to 7 hours of sleep at night. I
have to. If I don't, I feel it the next
day. And I'm dragging a little bit. I'm
not paying attention in meetings as
well. I'm not able to focus and really
dive into stuff. So there's an actual
physical reaction. I'm not mistaken. You
started this business in your kitchen.
In my kitchen? Yeah. 20.
Tell me how you started the business,
dude. I was like I was working in my
pajamas for like 6 months. Like
literally like I on this company. Yeah.
I had this white little desk in front of
this window and I had this Apple
computer like I started it in a really
personal like tragedy of in my life.
Like I had uh just gotten divorced. I
had two young kids and so I was like
literally just starting over and most
people probably would have just stayed
in a job or or went and got a great
salary and something like that. But I
really wanted to chase my dream man. I I
didn't want to be that guy that gave up.
And so every morning I would come
downstairs and I would start emailing,
you know, I had to get contracts with
insurance companies, right? Because we
live in a in an environment in the
United States where 97% of the
population is insured, right? They have
a health insurance that that they use.
And so I would literally go downstairs,
man, and I would be emailing insurance
companies and trying to get contracts
with insurance companies. And then I
would get up and then I would go out and
call on doctors and try to get business.
And then I leased a small office. It was
uh $500 a month and it was like 500
square f feet and I leased it and I
literally started. Talk to me about your
method in finding a winning product that
was able to generate hundreds of
millions of dollars. Well, I think
there's other products out there on the
marketplace, but I think what separates
us is everything that goes along with a
product. It's kind of like an iPhone,
right? Or a phone. Samsung has phones
that are equally as good as iPhone, but
the service level that you get with one
company versus another is really what's
important. And so for me, that's what I
focused on. And I didn't really say,
okay, I want to, you know, not only,
yes, I want to have a great product, but
if I don't have great service, it's not
going to win. You got to have both
combinations. What was the most amount
of money you've made in a single year?
Just in the last, you know, three or
four years, I probably added probably 85
million to my net worth. Are you
serious? 85 million. 85 million to my
net worth. Yeah. Just because I've
stayed focused. You got to be able to
figure out what moves the needle. That's
amazing. And what's the biggest thing
that is moving the needle? Like, how did
you scale your net worth? $85 million in
the last 3 to four years. Investing in
the right team. You got to have a team.
If you don't have a team, you got
nothing. You can't do it all yourself.
The reason that we hit the numbers we
hit and we have the success we have is
because we have an amazing team. And I
can't take credit for all of it. So, you
know, we have such an amazing team. But
I'll tell you that, you know, there was
a period in my career where my staff was
making more money than me. And I was
willing to do that because I wanted to
invest in my team. That's what helps you
scale. Like imagine like you can't run
650 employees by yourself. You can't.
You need the right team. And so there's
probably out of the 650 people I
probably talked to seven or eight. So,
who was the most important person that
you hired? You're looking at him,
actually. Yeah. You're looking at him,
man. I mean, I was number one. I was
number one. And then after that, it was
everybody else. And again, everyone has
done an amazing job. But, dude, at the
end of the day, it all comes down to
you. So, what's your superpower as a
business owner that you could give to
somebody else who may be struggling in
business right now? They're the CEO of
their company. They need that kind of
mindset shift like you to understand
that look, I'm the most important person
here. What's the single greatest value
ad that you as the CEO can add to your
business? You just got to believe in
yourself, man. You got to bet on you.
You got to believe in yourself. You got
to never quit, no matter how dark it
gets, cuz you'll have many, many dark
days. I've had many dark days. What was
the lowest point in your career? A
couple years ago, I was fighting a big
battle. Can't tell the details of it,
but it was a big battle. And there were
many dark moments, many dark days, many
dark weeks. And people ask me like,
well, how did you get through that? And
the truth of it is giving up was never
an option for me. I do believe in my
heart that if you really are committed
and you don't quit and you never give
up, you will get there. no matter how
smart or unsmart you may think you are
cuz I don't necessarily think I'm the
smartest guy, but what I do know is that
I'm never going to quit. Eventually,
you'll get there. So, what's been your
superpower as a business owner? I don't
think I see problems, man. You know how
like somebody says, "We're going to do
this and then everyone sees all the
problems." I just don't see the
problems. I do kind of want to go back
to thinking about hiring people. For an
entrepreneur, who are the three most
important people that they can hire to
grow their business in today's world?
Maybe it's not three, but if you can
think about a couple pivotal partners or
people that you brought in that really
helped you scale out a certain aspect of
your business, what roles or what would
that I think the first role that you
really need to make sure you have is a
great accountant. You need somebody
that's going to really manage your books
and manage your numbers correctly so
that you can really trust them because
at some point you're going to want to
sell your business. You're going to want
to go get lines of credit and you need
to be bankable. And in order to be
bankable, you need to have the right
accounting. Your numbers have to be
perfect cuz nobody's going to give you
any money if they're not. So they got to
be perfect. The second thing you need to
have is an ops person. You need somebody
that's really going to help you run ops.
Someone that's going to be in the weeds
helping you figure things out. And then
the third thing is because we're in a
technology world right now with AI and
everything else, you need a real good
CTO. You need somebody that's going to
help you that can think with your vision
of where you want to go and really help
you kind of plan out a 3 to 5year plan
of where to go and how to get there. And
if you have those three things, you're
good. But I'll tell you that the
accounting thing is probably the biggest
Achilles heel of most business owners.
Their accounting is a mess. Do you have
any great mentors? the guy that's flying
with me on the plane, you you think I'm
successful. This guy's like times 20,
okay? And and you know, he's a bit of an
older gentleman, but he's been my
mentor, somebody that I've looked up to
for many, many years. You guys should
actually have him on the show. But he's
a very successful businessman, and I've
learned a lot from him. I've learned a
lot from a lot of people that are
successful because I consider myself a
student. I think no matter how
successful you get in life, the best
entrepreneurs and the most successful
people always look at life as if they
are a student. I'm always trying to
learn something new. Always. The minute
you have that idea that you know
everything you've done, I don't want to
pigeon hole myself because somebody
could give me information that I could
use. So then they're a mentor to me. So
what is the best advice that you ever
receive from a mentor? Real quick, guys,
while we're on the topic of building
billion-dollar businesses, I want to
share with you one of the most powerful
lessons I've learned from a billionaire
entrepreneur. And it's that you don't
run a real business until you know your
numbers better than your product. And
that hit me hard because most
entrepreneurs don't fail from lack of
sales. They fail because their books are
a total disaster. And that's why I use
ODO accounting. It lets you send
professional invoices in seconds, track
payments, and follow up automatically,
so there's no chasing clients, which is
every business owner's nightmare. And
you can sync with over 28,000 banks
worldwide for real-time tracking and
reconcile everything with just the click
of a button. It even uses AI to scan and
input your expenses, so you're not stuck
doing manual data entry. The dashboards
are clean, the reports are instant, and
the entire system is designed to grow as
your business scales. And you want to
know the best part? The first app is
free for life with unlimited hosting and
support. So, if you're serious about
building a business that's sustainable,
check out ODU right now. All you have to
do is go down to the link in the
description of this video to try it
today for free. With that being said,
let's get back to the interview. Give me
something that's not typically taught in
a textbook or, you know, told to people
on a regular basis. Carl Icon said that
if you want to be very successful, you
have to be very shrewd. Shrewd. Shrewd.
You have to be very shrewd. What does
that mean? You have to count pennies and
you have to really think with the
details and you have to be willing to
have the uncomfortable conversations.
You have to be a shark. You can't be
ultra successful without being a shark.
Like I'm a shark. If you want to be a
successful businessman, you got to be a
shark. And if you're not willing to be a
shark, you're going to get stepped on.
You see something in the water, you bite
it. You bite it. Shark doesn't run.
Shark doesn't get in fear. Shark's like,
"Oh, dude, I'm going to bite you." And
that's how you have to be in the
business world. It's the most
competitive sport out there. What was
your go to market strategy? Was your
industry competitive when you went into
it? It was very competitive and there
were a lot of big players in the space.
I was a small guy. So throughout the
course, you know, a decade or so, some
of them went out of business, some of
them got sold, but we are now the number
one leader. Can you tell me the story
about how your competitors from when you
were in like high school or they were
like the number one? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
So, one of the biggest competitors that
went out of business in 2018, when I was
a senior in high school, they were in
business. So, they've been in business
for a really, really long time. And then
right around 2019, we surpassed them in
order volume. And we haven't looked back
ever since. And we've been the largest
player in the space since 2019. So, you
flanked them? Yeah, we flanked them and
we weren't around them and so 2019 so
was it like 6 years now? So 6 years now
we've been the number one player in the
country. What is your secret to standing
out in a competitive market? We have to
be very consistent as you know in order
to be successful in life you have to be
consistent on everything. So we've had
to deliver over and over and over again
all the time. You don't get a period of
time where you can just not deliver. So
we're on it every single day. Man, I'm
telling you, our team works around the
clock. Like we have an amazing team.
When you're seeing thousands of patients
every single day, there's no room for
errors. There's no room for mistakes.
You got to deliver consistently. Are you
a good salesman? I like to say that I am
a good salesman. Yeah, I like to say
that. Could you give me a piece of
negotiation advice? Cuz I know you've
closed some big deals. You've been at
the table with some heavy hitters. Give
me Give me your best sales and
negotiation advice for anybody in
business. If you're negotiating
something, don't ever give them the
first number. Don't be the guy to give
the first number. Make them make the
offer. Always make somebody else give
you the first number. Well, what if your
number's lower than theirs is? Why do
that? Was there a scenario that you did
that? There was a scenario that I was in
a negotiation with somebody helping a
friend of mine and he gave the first
number and I was so pissed. I'm like,
"Dude, why did you do that?" Cuz you
don't know what the other person was
thinking. So, I was just I was yelling
at him after the meeting. I'm like,
"Dude, why did you do that?" But I never
give the first number. Number one, but I
also think being a salesperson is not
being a gimmicky type person. It's being
real. It's being authentic. And I like
to say that I'm pretty authentic. So,
what you see is what you get. So, for
me, being sales is just, hey, I want to
talk to you about this and does it make
sense for you? If it doesn't make sense
for you, great. But if it does, then you
know, cool. Let's make a deal. So, let's
say you have a prospective client and
maybe they're leaning towards a no or
going with with somebody else. How do
you kind of bring them back in and get
them over to a yes? I'm not the salesman
that's going to try to say, "Pick me,
pick me." I'm not that guy. I want to
show you how valuable I am. And I want
you to decide if you think I'm the right
fit for you or not. There's 8 billion
people on the planet. Like, I'm not
going to lose sleep over one deal. So,
at the end of the day, I want you to
pick what's best for you because I
honestly believe that in my heart. I
want you, if you're buying something, to
get the best deal you possibly can for
you because that's going to make me
happy. If I'm not it, I'm not it. But
I'm never going to be like, "Pick me,
pick me." I'm just I'm just not that
guy. I like to be kind of like the prom
king or prom prom queen where it's like,
"Hey, I'm I'm waiting for everybody to
come to me." That's why I think every
day all I do is focus on value. I want
to go back to the the mentor aspect as
well cuz you gave me a beautiful piece
of advice about like you have to be
true. Do you have another one that that
a mentor taught you? So the guy that's
coming on the plane with me today, this
guy's super rich, right? He's super
rich. Rich, real money rich. One day I
was picking him up for his private
flight. This was years ago. And he's
like, "Hey, can we go to Panera Bread to
get bagels and coffee?" And I'm like,
"Why?" And he's like, "Well, because
they want to charge me, you know, $250
on the jet." I guess he was chartering a
jet. And I'm like, "Dude," I'm like, "
$250 is nothing for you." He's like,
"Yeah, but you know what, Vic? That's
not what it costs." I'm like, "What?
What do you mean?" He said, "A jet costs
what a jet costs. Fuel for a jet costs
what a jet costs. $2,500 an hour for jet
fuel, whatever. Bagels and coffee
doesn't cost $275." And it just hit me
like a ton of bricks, man. I'm like, no
matter how wealthy this guy is, he's
still thinking with the general
principles of business and life. And
he's like, it doesn't cost that.
Farragama shoes cost 500 bucks. That's
what it costs. Bagels and coffee don't
cost 275 bucks. Okay. That's the real
spill right now. Yeah. So, he goes out.
I'll show you this. So, we go out and we
go to Panera Bread. And I got one now,
too, so I can pull it out. And he pulls
this out. It's a black card. Pulls out
the black card. He buys the bagels and
coffee and it was like seven bucks. We
get on the car. We go back to the
airport and we leave. And that was it.
And it taught me such a lesson, man. You
can never forget about what things cost
in business cuz then you'll overspend.
How much did the jet cost? I would say
all of it is over $5 million bucks. $5
million. Now, is it safe to say that you
can fake a supercar, but you can't fake
a private jet? You can't fake a private
jet. Even if somebody gave you a jet,
you still need $2 million a year to
[__] run the jet. If somebody gave
you a jet, so that's why you can't fake
a jet. If somebody gave you a jet, you'd
have to have at least $2 million a year
to just run it, just to run it. How many
entrepreneurs do you think are faking
the life that they're living? I think
95% of them are are You can see through
it. Yeah, I can. I I can see through it.
I can smell it. There's certain things
you just can't fake. And if you're
making so much money, why are you not
living life to the fullest? Especially
if you're a business person, you got a
lot of people, entrepreneurs and
influencers today and they're on
Instagram and they're like, "Yeah, I'm
making $100 million a week." Okay, well,
if you're making $100 million a week,
why are you flying commercial? Where's
your plane? Why wouldn't you have a
plane? If you're making that much money,
why wouldn't you have a plane? It's the
ultimate convenience. Like, it's the
ultimate convenience. It's that's why
it's the ultimate privilege. And so it's
like I I sniff that [__] out. Dude, do
you uh do you make more money when
you're flying private? I do because it
makes me feel good. So you step into
that frequency and that in turn helps
you make a lot more. It makes me think.
I I get the right people on my plane,
talk to them, get ideas from them,
understand things, all that stuff. Like
even right now, see the Escalade pulling
up? That's my wife and my kids. And I
get to fly with them now. And then I get
to go work and do all this stuff, which
I couldn't do if I was doing it any
other way. Do you network with a lot of
billionaires? Yeah, way more since I got
the plane. Now I can call them up like,
"Hey dude, I'm flying to blah blah blah.
Can you come?" What have you learned
from billionaires that they do
differently from everybody else? They're
just more shark. They're more hustling.
They're more into it. They're more
passionate. And I wouldn't say by a
large number, but just that little bit
of an edge where they're like, you know
what? I just want more. And that makes a
lot of difference, man. It's like water
bowls at 212, not at 211. Do you think
everybody's built for entrepreneurship?
Hell no. Hell hell no. Why not? Hell no.
Most people don't have the stomach for
it, man. They really don't. You got to
be willing to deal with everything. And
if you're not, don't do it. How old are
you now? I'm 48. If you were to go back
in time and have a conversation with
your 20-year-old self, what's the best
advice you'd give to your younger self?
Spend the first 30 learning, spend the
next 30 earning, and spend the last 30
giving. Learn, learn, learn, and then
earn, earn, earn. Did you go to college?
I did not. I have a high school diploma.
But you made more than 99.9% of business
professors ever will. Oh, yeah. So, give
me a lesson about business that is
nowhere to be found in any school
curriculum, even at Harvard Business
School. I think be practical. A lot of
times you get lost in the minutia of
trying to be complicated. The best
compliment that I feel like I can be
told as a businessman is you're so
simple. And if you look at the most
successful entrepreneurs, they look at
everything in a very simple way and they
can break everything down into on a
calculator and they can break it all
down into a paragraph as opposed to an
hourong conversation. Abraham Lincoln
said that a long time ago. He says, "If
you can't summarize something in the
sentence, you don't know it well
enough." What's more important in the
business world? What you know or who you
know? They're both. Both. Which one's
more important in this season of your
life? Both. No, both. Because because
you got to know the information, but
then you got to know the right person to
talk to. You got to know the right
person. Did you consistently build
relationships with the right people?
Invest in them. Invest in getting in
front of the right people. Buying a
plane. I didn't have to stretch and buy
a plan. Did you pay a lot for
mentorship? I never paid a lot. Well, I
guess I would say this. I paid a lot for
mentorship in kind of a roundabout way,
right? Because buying a plane allowed me
to get in front of bigger mentors that I
wouldn't have been able to. And that's
that's a fact. Spending money in myself
and investing in myself was by far the
best the best thing I've ever done in my
life because there's the one thing
nobody can ever take away from you is
your ability. They can take your plane
away. They can take your car away. They
can take your house away. They can take
everything away. They can't take away
what's in here. Did you have a lot of
money when you started your business? I
did not. I had literally no money. I had
no money. I was in debt, credit card
debt. I I raised money, friends and
family, but I had no money. I had no net
worth. Zero. Nothing, man. I was I had
nothing. And your last message to
somebody trying to own a private jet in
today's world? We're sitting on a
private jet right now. A lot of people
dream to own a private jet. Give them
the blueprint right here. 60-second
blueprint on how somebody can own a
private jet in today's world. Take a lot
of risk, start a business, build it up,
create an immense amount of cash flow
and revenue. And if you do that
consistently year over year over year
over year, you will eventually get
there. The big question to a lot of
people is how much money do you need to
make to afford a private jet? I would
tell you that you probably need at least
$2 to $3 million a year in just
disposable income to be able to afford a
private jet. You got amazing advice, my
friend. Yeah, thanks. Thank you so much
for your time. Thanks for having me,
man. I really appreciate you, Vic. Where
can everybody find you at, man? You can
follow me. I'm on every platform. My
handle is vicip I cip n. Google me,
you'll see me, you'll see the rise
conference, you'll see everything. Guys,
be sure to follow Vic. We're going to
put the links down to him below. Be sure
to like and subscribe for incredible
content we've got coming every single
week with the biggest business owners in
the world. And if you're not a member
yet, guys, we built the number one
community online for business owners in
the entire world, the School of Mentors,
where every single week I bring in the
millionaires and the billionaires that I
interview on this channel to mentor you
and answer any questions that you have
about business, anything. So, if you
want to join, go down to the link in the
description to become a member of the
School of Mentors today. I can't wait to
see you on the inside. With that being
said, I'll see you in the next